fusiondrupalthemes.com 2011-01-07

# Privacy policy | Fusion Drupal Themes Shop

Your privacy is critically important to us. We have a few fundamental principles:

We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.  
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.  
We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

Collective Mind LLC (“Collective Mind”) operates several websites, including fusiondrupalthemes.com and topnotchthemes.com. It is Collective Mind’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Collective Mind collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Collective Mind’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Collective Mind’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Collective Mind may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Collective Mind also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Collective Mind does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Collective Mind’s websites choose to interact with Collective Mind in ways that require Collective Mind to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Collective Mind gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who register for an account on fusiondrupalthemes.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Collective Mind – by purchasing a premium Drupal theme, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Collective Mind collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Collective Mind. Collective Mind does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Aggregated Statistics

Collective Mind may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Collective Mind may monitor the number of postings by users on its site, or use spam screened by the Mollom service to help identify spam. Collective Mind may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Collective Mind does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Collective Mind discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Collective Mind’s behalf or to provide services available at Collective Mind’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Collective Mind’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Collective Mind will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Collective Mind discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Collective Mind believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Collective Mind, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Collective Mind website and have supplied your email address, Collective Mind may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Collective Mind and our products. We primarily use our blog and forums to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Collective Mind takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Collective Mind uses cookies to help Collective Mind identify and track visitors, their usage of Collective Mind websites, and their website access preferences. Collective Mind visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Collective Mind’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Collective Mind’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Comments

Comments and other content submitted to the Mollom anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Collective Mind may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Collective Mind’s sole discretion. Collective Mind encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

## about

Fusion Drupal Themes are brought to you by TopNotchThemes, the premier shop for [Drupal themes](http://fusiondrupalthemes.com/) and custom theming. 

Established in 2007, we're based in San Francisco, California.
